{
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "prompt": "Why did the chicken cross the road?",
      "cpuResponse": "To get to the other side.",
      "cpuLikes": 8,
      "userResponse": "Cuz KFC was on his side.",
      "userLikes": 6,
      "username": "Bobby"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "prompt": "What did the fish say when he swam into the wall?",
      "cpuResponse": "Dam.",
      "cpuLikes": 6,
      "userResponse": "Beeeeeeaaaach.",
      "userLikes": 11,
      "username": "Min"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "prompt": "What do you call a fish with no eyes?",
      "cpuResponse": "A fsh.",
      "cpuLikes": 18,
      "userResponse": "Blind.",
      "userLikes": 2,
      "username": "Nick"
    },
    {
      "prompt": "I can't believe I got fired from the calendar factory.",
      "cpuResponse": "All I did was take a day off.",
      "cpuLikes": 4,
      "userResponse": "ohohoh",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "jane",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "prompt": "A Roman walks into a bar and raises 2 fingers and says to the bartender...",
      "cpuResponse": "\"Five beers, please.\"",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "because 7 8 9",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What do you call a witch at the beach?",
      "cpuResponse": "A Sandwich.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "sand",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "jane",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What kind of car did Whitney Houston drive?",
      "cpuResponse": "A Hyundaiiiiiiiiiiii",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "the bodyguard",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "mj",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Why do cows wear bells?",
      "cpuResponse": "Because their horns don't work!",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "moo",
      "userLikes": 1,
      "userName": "jm",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "prompt": "I just got fired from my job at the keyboard factory.",
      "cpuResponse": "They told me I wasn't putting in enough shifts.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "hoho",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "barb",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Has COVID-19 forced you to wear glasses and a mask at the same time?",
      "cpuResponse": "If so, you may be entitled to condensation.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "no i dead",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "phil",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "prompt": "So I made a graph of all my past relationships.",
      "cpuResponse": "It has an ex axis and a why axis.",
      "cpuLikes": 1,
      "userResponse": "",
      "userLikes": 1,
      "userName": "",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Why did the koala get rejected?",
      "cpuResponse": "Because he did not have any koalafication.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "he did not have the correct koalafications",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Which part of the hospital has the least privacy?",
      "cpuResponse": "The ICU.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "hallway",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "bobby",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Why did the chicken cross the road, roll in the mud and cross the road again?",
      "cpuResponse": "He was a dirty double-crosser!",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "popeye",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "sarah",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What did the cell say when his sister cell stepped on his foot?",
      "cpuResponse": "Mitosis.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "mi toe sis",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "paul",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What do you call a witch at the beach?",
      "cpuResponse": "A Sandwich.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "earthbender",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "prompt": "A grocery store cashier asked if I would like my milk in a bag.",
      "cpuResponse": "I told her \"No, thanks. The carton works fine\".",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "yes",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "prompt": "A Roman walks into a bar and raises 2 fingers and says to the bartender...",
      "cpuResponse": "\"Five beers, please.\"",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "5 drinks plz",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "min",
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What kind of car did Whitney Houston drive?",
      "cpuResponse": "A Hyundaiiiiiiiiiiii",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "no",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "prompt": "No matter how kind you are...",
      "cpuResponse": "German kids are always Kinder.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "eat",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "namu",
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "prompt": "To prove he was right, the flat-earther walked to the end of the Earth.",
      "cpuResponse": "He eventually came around.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "to this day he is still walking",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "min",
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Did you hear about the claustrophobic astronaut?",
      "cpuResponse": "He just needed a little space.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "no",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "lisa",
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What do you call a cow with no legs?",
      "cpuResponse": "Ground beef.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "ground beef",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "sally",
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Where do sick cruise ships go to get healthy?",
      "cpuResponse": "The dock!",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "the doctor silly",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "jane",
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "prompt": "No matter how kind you are...",
      "cpuResponse": "German kids are always Kinder.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "you will go to hell",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "robbie",
      "id": 25
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What's the best thing about Switzerland?",
      "cpuResponse": "I don't know, but the flag is a big plus.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "fondue",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "bobbie",
      "id": 26
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Do you know what killed the man who had a two ton pumpkin fall on him?",
      "cpuResponse": "He was squashed.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "the seeds",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "nick",
      "id": 27
    },
    {
      "prompt": "I was feeling depressed, my wife put her hand on my back and said \"Earth.\"",
      "cpuResponse": "It meant the world to me.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "flat ass",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "tim",
      "id": 28
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Has COVID-19 forced you to wear glasses and a mask at the same time?",
      "cpuResponse": "If so, you may be entitled to condensation.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "condensation",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "timmy",
      "id": 29
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What happened to the man who got behind on payments to his exorcist?",
      "cpuResponse": "He got repossessed.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "idk man",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "bobby",
      "id": 30
    },
    {
      "prompt": "My employer came running to me and said, \"I was looking for you all day! Where the hell have you been?\"",
      "cpuResponse": "I replied, \"Good employees are hard to find.\"",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "stopastopstop",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "bobby",
      "id": 31
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What's the difference between a poorly dressed man on a unicycle and a well dressed man on a bicycle?",
      "cpuResponse": "Attire.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "no",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 32
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Which part of the hospital has the least privacy?",
      "cpuResponse": "The ICU.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "ohohoh",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 33
    },
    {
      "prompt": "How much did your chimney cost?",
      "cpuResponse": "Nothing, it was on the house.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "ohohoh",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 34
    },
    {
      "prompt": "I can't believe I got fired from the calendar factory.",
      "cpuResponse": "All I did was take a day off.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "jghgh",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "vcg",
      "id": 35
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Why does the size of the snack not matter to a giraffe?",
      "cpuResponse": "Because even a little bit goes a long way.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "sdfsdfsdfsdf",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "dsfd",
      "id": 36
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What did the customer say to the waiter?",
      "cpuResponse": "I'm all fed up with your service.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "SHUTUP",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "SALLY",
      "id": 37
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What did the customer say to the waiter?",
      "cpuResponse": "I'm all fed up with your service.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "SHUTUP",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "SALLY",
      "id": 38
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What did the customer say to the waiter?",
      "cpuResponse": "I'm all fed up with your service.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "SHUTUP",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "SALLY",
      "id": 39
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What do you call 4 Mexicans in quicksand?",
      "cpuResponse": "Quatro Sinko.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "because 7 8 9",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "min",
      "id": 40
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What do you call 4 Mexicans in quicksand?",
      "cpuResponse": "Quatro Sinko.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "sus",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "min",
      "id": 41
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What time did the man go to the dentist?",
      "cpuResponse": "Tooth hurt-y.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "sdjfnsjdnksf",
      "userLikes": 9,
      "userName": "nsdfbjsdf",
      "id": 42
    },
    {
      "prompt": "I walked into a bar once.",
      "cpuResponse": "It really hurt my head.",
      "cpuLikes": 3,
      "userResponse": "cool ",
      "userLikes": 6,
      "userName": "joe",
      "id": 43
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Did you hear about the crime in the parking garage?",
      "cpuResponse": "It was wrong on so many levels.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "ohohoh",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 44
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Did you hear about the crime in the parking garage?",
      "cpuResponse": "It was wrong on so many levels.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "ohohoh",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 45
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Why did the chicken cross the road, roll in the mud and cross the road again?",
      "cpuResponse": "He was a dirty double-crosser!",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "chicken",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "sarah",
      "id": 46
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Why did the chicken cross the road, roll in the mud and cross the road again?",
      "cpuResponse": "He was a dirty double-crosser!",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "chicken",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "sarah",
      "id": 47
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Why did the chicken cross the road, roll in the mud and cross the road again?",
      "cpuResponse": "He was a dirty double-crosser!",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "chickentoo",
      "userLikes": 2,
      "userName": "mark",
      "id": 48
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Where do sick cruise ships go to get healthy?",
      "cpuResponse": "The dock!",
      "cpuLikes": 2,
      "userResponse": "the bodyguard",
      "userLikes": 3,
      "userName": "justin",
      "id": 49
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Do you know what killed the man who had a two ton pumpkin fall on him?",
      "cpuResponse": "He was squashed.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "yes man 1",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "jane",
      "id": 50
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Do you know what killed the man who had a two ton pumpkin fall on him?",
      "cpuResponse": "He was squashed.",
      "cpuLikes": 0,
      "userResponse": "yes man 2",
      "userLikes": 0,
      "userName": "sarah",
      "id": 51
    }
  ]
}